<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Andy&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://www.significantly-insignificant.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Andy&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.significantly-insignificant.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Networking 101</title>
      <link>https://www.significantly-insignificant.com/post/networking-101/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.significantly-insignificant.com/post/networking-101/</guid>
      <description>Networking, as defined by the Oxford dictionary, is the &amp;ldquo;action or process of interacting with others to exchange information and develop professional or social contacts&amp;rdquo;.
Networking, as defined by my past experiences, is the &amp;ldquo;action or process where I get to dress fancy and drink beers with professionals from prospective fields, however given that I&amp;rsquo;m a lightweight but also slightly alcoholic, slowly get drunk off like 2 pints whilst trying my hardest to remain professional and not slur while talking with the CEO of the biggest superannuation company in Austrlaia&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://www.significantly-insignificant.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2019 14:04:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.significantly-insignificant.com/about/</guid>
      <description>This is a creation arising from sheer boredom and the very essence of procrastination - the exact, stereotypical combination of elements surrounding your typical university student. I&amp;rsquo;ve got 2 exams that I&amp;rsquo;ve got to study for, but goddamn 2 shots of coffee really goes a long way to keep me distracted from doing actual work.
I intend to use this as a way to keep track of anything &amp;amp; everything interesting with my life (so realistically not much).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Testing, attention please</title>
      <link>https://www.significantly-insignificant.com/post/testing-attention-please/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.significantly-insignificant.com/post/testing-attention-please/</guid>
      <description>10:32pm
Just bought the domain &amp;ldquo;significantly-insignificant&amp;rdquo; for about $11. Currently trying to upload a static version of this blog online. But holy shit is it hard. I&amp;rsquo;ve spent literally the whole night fixing bugs and googling my way through how to build the site via Netlify, but goddam this is difficult.
I&amp;rsquo;m going to go through the &amp;ldquo;rubber ducky&amp;rdquo; approach, where I explain my troubleshooting &amp;amp; thought process step by step:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>